DAVID BALDUS PAPERS (APAP329) 1965-2011
M. E. Grenander Department of Special Collections and Archives
- Material form the Defenders' Association of Philadelphia, 1985-2008; 12; 84.7
  - Subject Files, 1998-2006; 12.7; 11.8
    - notes- dave adams, Undated (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - Notes- doc phone contacts, Undated (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - Out of county materials, 1990; 1992-1995; Undated (Box 5, Folder 18)
    - Overview of argument againest death penalty (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - Penalty trial case summaries- death penalty cases- page 1 thru 205, Undated (Box 5, Folder 20)
    - Penalty trial case summaries- death penalty cases- page 1 thru 272, Undated (Box 5, Folder 21)
    - Penalty trial case summaries- life sentence cases- pages 273 thru 324, Undated (Box 5, Folder 22)
    - Penalty trial case summaries- no penalty/life sentences- pages 2A thru 151, Undated (Box 5, Folder 23)
    - Penalty trial case summaries- no penalty/life sentences- pages 151A thru 310, Undated (Box 5, Folder 24)
    - Pennsylvania charging and sentencing study- sampling plan, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 25)
    - Pennsylvania commission on sentencing- encoded data for murder 1 sentences, Undated (Box 5, Folder 26)
    - Pennsylvania courts review form- murder of the first degree, 1993-1995; Undated (Box 5, Folder 27)
    - Pennsylvania death penalty project- intern paperwork, Undated (Box 5, Folder 28)
    - Pennsylvania proportionality review DCI- Blank Forms, 1995-1996 (Box 5, Folder 29)
    - Pennsylvania proportionality review DCI- Blank forms, 1997-1998 (Box 5, Folder 30)
    - Pennsylvania proportionality review DCI- Coding instructions, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 31)
    - Pennsylvania proportionality review DCI- Filled In-B, 1996; Undated (Box 5, Folder 32)
    - Pennsylvania proportionality review DCI- Filled in-C, Undated (Box 5, Folder 33)
    - Pennsylvania Proportionality review Dci- Filled In- D, 1996; Undated (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Pennsylvania Proportionality review DCI- Filled in- E thru G, 1996-1997; Undated (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Pennsylvania proportionality review DCI- filled in-H, 1996; Undated (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Pennsylvania proportionality review DCI- filled in-I, Undated (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Pennsylvania proportionality review DCI- filled in-K, Undated (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Pennsylvania proportionality review DCI- filled in-L, Undated (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Pennsylvania proportionality review DCI- Filled- in m thru O, Undated (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Pennsylvania Proportionality review DCI- Filled in-P, Undated (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Pennsylvania proportionality review DCI- Filled in- R, 1996; Undated (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Pennsylvania Proportionality Review Dci- filled in- S, 1996; Undated (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - Pennsylvania proportionality review DCI- filled in-T, Undated (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Pennsylvania Proportionality Review DCI- filled in- V, Undated (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - Pennsylvania proportionality review DCI- filled in- Wallace thru Whalen, 1996; Undated (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - pennsylvania proportionality review DCI- filled in- Wheeler thru Williams, alan, 1996; Undated (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - Pennsylvania proportionality review DCI- filled in- williams, 1996; Undated (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - Pennsylvania proportionality reviw DCI- Filled in- Williamson thru worthy, 1996; Undated (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - Pennsylvania Proportionality review DCI- Filled in-Y, 1996 (Box 6, Folder 17)
    - Pennsylvania Proportionality review Dci- filled in- Z, 1996; Undated (Box 6, Folder 18)
    - Pennsylvania Proportionality review supplemental DCI- Blank Forms, 1995; Undated (Box 6, Folder 19)
    - Pennsylvania proportionality review DCI- filled in-A and B, 1996; Undated (Box 6, Folder 20)
    - Pennsylvania proportionality review DCI- filled in- C thru G, 1996; Undated (Box 6, Folder 21)
    - Pennsylvania Proportionality Review Supplemental DCI- Filled in- H thru L, 1996; Undated (Box 6, Folder 22)
    - Pennsylvania proportionality review supplemental Dci- filled in- m thru P, 1996; Undated (Box 6, Folder 23)
    - Pennsylvania proportionality review supplemental DCI- R thru S, 1996; Undated (Box 6, Folder 24)
    - Pennsylvania proportionality review supplemental DCI- filled in- T thru Z, 1996; Undated (Box 6, Folder 25)
    - Pennsylvania sample for capital jurors project, 1996 (Box 6, Folder 26)
    - Pennsylvania Sentencing guideline study- research materials, 2002; Undated (Box 6, Folder 27)
    - Philadelphia capital juror project- supplemental plan, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 28)
    - Philadelphia capital juror project- supplemental plan- drafts, notes, and statistical print outs, 1998-1999; Undated (Box 6, Folder 29)
    - Philadelphia capital juror project- supplemental plan- Plan and Appendices A thru F, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 30)
    - Philadelphia capital juor project- supplemental plan- appendices G, H, and K, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 31)
    - Philadelphia capital juror project- supplemental plan- appendix A update, 1999 (Box 6, Folder 32)
    - Philadelphia capital juror project- supplemental plan 6/99- rough draft/notes, 1999; Undated (Box 6, Folder 33)
    - Philadelphia case files- clarence adams, 2003 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Philadelphia case files- keith andrews, 2002 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Philadelphia case files- michael Andrews, 2002 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Philadelphia case files- Mitchell ash, 2002-2003 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Philadelphia case files- Yakee Bentley, 2002 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Philadelphia case files- Reginald Bryant, 2002-2003 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Philadelphia case files- Dallas Bullock, 2002-2003 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Philadelphia case files- William case, 2002 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Philadelphia case files- Zebbie clifton, 2002 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Philadelphia case files- bernard Cousar, 2002-2003 (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Philadelphia case files- German Cruz, 1999; 2001; Undated (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Philadelphia case files- German Cruz- jury selection notes, 1997-2000; 2002; Undated (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - Philadelphia case files- Blandon everett, 2002 (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - Philadelphia case files- Lester fletcher, 2003 (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - Philadelphia case files- Edwin Gomez, 2002 (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - Philadelphia case files- javier goode, 2001; 2003 (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - Philadelphia case files- Wendell Graves, 2002-2003 (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - Philadelphia case files- Sherman Gravitt, 2003 (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - Philadelphia case files- Vincent Hatcher, 2002-2003 (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - Philadelphia case files- richard Heary, 2002-2003 (Box 7, Folder 20)
    - Philadelphia case files- Steven Holiday, 2003 (Box 7, Folder 21)
    - Philadelphia case files- Rhonshawn Jackson, 2002 (Box 7, Folder 22)
    - Philadelphia case files- Earl Lilly, 2002-2003 (Box 7, Folder 23)
    - Philadelphia case Files- Jonathan Little, 2002 (Box 7, Folder 24)
    - Philadelphia case files- James Lomax, 2003 (Box 7, Folder 25)
    - Philadelphia case files- jose martinez, 2002 (Box 7, Folder 26)
    - Philadelphia case files- John Ming, 2002 (Box 7, Folder 27)
    - Philadelphia case files- Antonio Molina, 2003 (Box 7, Folder 28)
    - Philadelphia case files- quanguan Nguyen, 2003 (Box 7, Folder 29)
    - Philadelphia case files- larry Nicolas, 2002-2003 (Box 7, Folder 30)
    - Philadelphia case files- jason O'Neil, 2002-2003 (Box 7, Folder 31)
    - Philadelphia case files- Joseph Paige, 2003 (Box 7, Folder 32)
    - Philadelphia case files- Stephen Palmer, 2002-2003 (Box 7, Folder 33)
    - Philadelphia case files- bernard Pogue, 2002 (Box 7, Folder 34)
    - Philadelphia case files- franciso Querendongo, 2002 (Box 7, Folder 35)
    - Philadelphia case files- Omar Richardson, 2002-2003 (Box 7, Folder 36)
    - Philadelphia case files- Rafael Rojas, 2002 (Box 7, Folder 37)
    - Philadelphia case files- gregory samuels, 2002-2003 (Box 7, Folder 38)
    - Philadelphia case files- Marcus Scott, 2002-2003; Undated (Box 7, Folder 39)
    - Philadelphia case files- david Sheppard, 2003 (Box 7, Folder 40)
    - Philadelphia case files- willie Singletary, 2002 (Box 7, Folder 41)
    - Philadelphia case files- Damon Walls, 2002-2003 (Box 7, Folder 42)
    - Philadelphia case files- Robert wead, 2003 (Box 7, Folder 43)
    - Philadelphia case files- Khalid Wilcox, 2002-2003 (Box 7, Folder 44)
    - Philadelphia case files- thomas Wisniewski, 2002-2003 (Box 7, Folder 45)
    - Philadelphia case files- Jamal Wright, 2002 (Box 7, Folder 46)
    - Philadelphia case files- christopher Young, 1999-2001; Undated (Box 7, Folder 47)
    - Philadelphia homicide severity study- exhibits a-c, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 48)
    - Philadelphia Homicide Severity study- Exhibits D1 and D2, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 49)
    - philadelphia homicide severity study- exhibits e-I, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 50)
    - Philadelphia homicide severity study survey- Rater 3 deck a-a, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 51)
    - Philadelphia homicide severity study survey- rater 7 deck B-A, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 52)
    - Philadelphia homicide severity study survey- rater 8 deck J, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 53)
    - Philadelphia juror study- draft of outline, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 54)
    - Philadelphia thumbs to be reviewed- Case summaries, Undated (Box 7, Folder 55)
    - Philadelphia thumbs to be reviewed- Case summaries- checked, Undated (Box 7, Folder 56)
    - Philadelphia thumbs to be reviewed- correspondence, notes, and statistical printouts, 1996-1997; Undated (Box 7, Folder 57)
    - Preliminary report on the rate of death penalty exposure in Philadelphia county, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 58)
    - Project numbers and list of variables to be coded, Undated (Box 7, Folder 59)
    - Re-wild code notes, 1996; Undated (Box 7, Folder 60)
    - reference materials- coding case summaries, Undated (Box 7, Folder 61)
    - Refrence materials- evolving stnadards of decency- The aboliton of the death penalty, Undated (Box 7, Folder 62)
    - Reference materials- evolving standards of decency- abolition of the death penalty: an emergency norm of international law, 2002 (Box 7, Folder 63)
    - Reference materials- evolving standards of decency- amnesty international, 2002 (Box 7, Folder 64)
    - Reference materials- evolving standards of decency- daryl renard atkins v. virgina, 2002 (Box 7, Folder 65)
    - Reference materials- evolving standards of decency- Back to an international perspective on the death penalty as a punishment, 2002 (Box 7, Folder 66)
    - Reference materials- evolving standards of decenecy- a death penalty primer, 2002 (Box 7, Folder 67)
    - Reference materials- evolving standards of decency- europe: a death penalty free zone, 2002 (Box 7, Folder 68)
    - Reference materials- evolving standards of decency- the international judicial dialogue, 2002 (Box 7, Folder 69)
    - Reference materials- evolving standards of decency- international law and the aboliton of the death penalty, 2002 (Box 7, Folder 70)
    - Reference materials- evolving standards of decency- ernest paul mccarver v. north carolina, 2002 (Box 7, Folder 71)
    - reference materials- evolving standards of decency- a paradox, 2002 (Box 7, Folder 72)
    - Reference materials- evolving standards of decency- paying "decent respect" to world opinion on the death penalty, 2002 (Box 7, Folder 73)
    - reference materials- evolving standards of decency- Playing for keeps, 2002 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Reference materials- evolving standards of decency- The supreme court and the law of nations, 2002 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Reference materials- evolving standards of decency- The United States: "Capital" of the world, 2002 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Reference materials- evolving standards of decency- united states statistics, 2002; Undated (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Reference materials- evolving standards of decency- untitled, Undated (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Reference materials- how to file with intenational organizations- Law review article procedure, 2002 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Reference materials- how to file petitions with international organizations- literature and notes, 2003; Undated (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Reference materials- How to file petitions with international organizations- Oas, 1503, and committees, 2002; Undated (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Reference materials- How to file petitions with international organizations- vienna convention, 2002 (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Sentencing commission reports- non-philadelphia, 1996; Undated (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Sentencing commission reports- philadelphia, Undated (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - Severity study- case summaries- A thru C, 1997; Undated (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - Severity study- case summaries- D thru g, 1997; Undated (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - Severity study- case summaries- H thru J, 1997; Undated (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - Severity study- case summaries- K thru M, 1997; Undated (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - Severity study- Case summaries- N thru P, Undated (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - Severity study- case summaries- R thru S, 1997; Undated (Box 8, Folder 17)
    - Severity study- Case summaries- T,W, and Y, 1997; Undated (Box 8, Folder 18)
    - Severity study- Draft listing of brief case summaries, Undated (Box 8, Folder 19)
    - Severity study- Drafts of case summary ranking cards, 1996; Undated (Box 8, Folder 20)
    - Severity study- list of philly and non-philly coded cases, Undated (Box 8, Folder 21)
    - Severity study- Narrative review checklist, Undated (Box 8, Folder 22)
    - Severity study- notes and case details with variables, 1997; Undated (Box 8, Folder 23)
    - Severity study- Reference materials, 1980; 1986; 1995-1997 (Box 8, Folder 24)
    - Severity study- reference materials, Undated (Box 8, Folder 25)
    - Skin-tone study- case details- Abbott thru Caufield, 1980-1988; 1990-1993; Undated (Box 8, Folder 26)
    - Skin-tone study- case details- chase thru Collins, 1982; 1985; 1988; 1993; Undated (Box 8, Folder 27)
    - Skin-tone study- case details- cook thru fahy, 1983; 1987-1988; 1990-1993; 1996; Undated (Box 8, Folder 28)
    - Skin-tone study- case details- Felder thru Horsey, 1981; 1983-1984; 1987; 1989-1993; Undated (Box 8, Folder 29)
    - Skin-tone study- case details- Howard thru Lewis, 1982-1985; 1987; 1990; 1992; Undated (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Skin-tone study- case details- lowry thru pelzer, 1982-1984; 1986; 1989-1993; Undated (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Skin-tone study- case details- peoples thru Royster, 1984-1986; 1990-1993; 1995; Undated (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Skin-tone study- Case details- Rucker thru torres, 1982; 1984; 1990-1994; 1999; Undated (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Skin-tone study-case details- Tran thru young, 1981; 1983-1986; 1989; 1992-1993; Undated (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Skin-tone study- case details- unidentified case materials, 1982; 1990; 1993; Undated (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Skin-tone study- Philadelphia county- inmate details- Au-Jamal thru Pryer, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - Skin-tone study- philadelphia county- inmate details- pulley thru young, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - Skin-tone study- Philadelphia county- summary of inmate details, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Skin-tone study- Philadelphia county and out of county- Inmate details- barron thru yost, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - Skin-tone study- philadelphia county and out of county- inmate details- bnon-African American- Abbott thru Zook, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - Skin-tone study- Philadelphia county and out of county- summary of inmate details- non-african American, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - Skin-tone study- out of county- inmate details- African Americans- Adams thru williams, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - Skin-tone study- out of county- summary of inmate details- African Americans, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - Statistics- defense assets, 1995 (Box 9, Folder 15)
    - Superior court of Pennsylvania Opinions, 1992; 1994 (Box 9, Folder 16)
    - Technical Appendices 10 & 11, 1997; Undated (Box 9, Folder 17)
    - Unfiled court and police documents, 1987; 1993-1995; Undated (Box 9, Folder 18)
    - Unfiled court and police documents- A and B, 1983-1984; 1986; 1988; 1990; 1997 (Box 9, Folder 19)
    - Unfiled court and police documents- A and B, 1995; Undated (Box 9, Folder 20)
    - Unfiled court and police documents- C, D and G RESTRICTED, 1985; 1989-1992; 1995; Undated (Box 9, Folder 21)
    - unfiled court and police documents- H, Undated (Box 9, Folder 22)
    - Unfiled court and police documents- h,J and L, 1980; 1983; 1985; 1990; 1992-1995 (Box 9, Folder 23)
    - Unfiled court and police documents- M, 1990-1992; 1995; Undated (Box 9, Folder 24)
    - Unfiled court and police documents- O and P, 1983; 1992; 1995 (Box 9, Folder 25)
    - Unfiled court and police documents- R, 1981; 1985; 1987; 1990 (Box 9, Folder 26)
    - Unfiled court and police documents- R, 1992; 1995 (Box 9, Folder 27)
    - Unfiled court and police documents-S, 1983-1985; 1987; 1990-1992; 1995; Undated (Box 9, Folder 28)
    - Unfiled court and police documents- t,W and Y, 1988; 1990; 1995; Undated (Box 9, Folder 29)
    - Uniform crime report- commonwealth of pennsylvania- annual report, 1993 (Box 9, Folder 30)
    - variable list-By age range, Undated (Box 9, Folder 31)
    - Variable list- cases in 1983-1993 with no narratives, 1997 (Box 9, Folder 32)
    - variable lists- check Juror, 1998 (Box 9, Folder 33)
    - variable list- miles, 1998 (Box 9, Folder 34)
    - Variable list- Non-ph phi, Undated (Box 9, Folder 35)
    - Variable list- Willdo, 1998 (Box 9, Folder 36)
    - Variable names and descriptions- death penalty eligible cases, 1994; Undated (Box 9, Folder 37)
    - Voir dire sheets- Richard Abbott, 1997; Undated (Box 9, Folder 38)
    - Voir dire sheets- Mumia Abu-journal, 1982 (Box 9, Folder 39)
    - Voir dire sheets- James adams, Undated (Box 9, Folder 40)
    - Voir dire sheets- Luis Alamo, Undated (Box 9, Folder 41)
    - Voir dire sheets- Johnny h. Alexander, et. Al., 1988 (Box 9, Folder 42)
    - Voir dire sheets- jamal allen, et. Al., Undated (Box 9, Folder 43)
    - Voir dire sheets- Michael anderson, Undated (Box 9, Folder 44)
    - voir dire sheets- lee baker, et. Al., Undated (Box 9, Folder 45)
    - Voir dire sheets- David Barham, et. Al, Undated (Box 9, Folder 46)
    - Voir dice sheets- randolph barksdale, Undated (Box 9, Folder 47)
    - Voir dire sheets- Yennis baxter, Undated (Box 9, Folder 48)
    - Voir dire sheets- Theresa battles, et. Al., Undated (Box 9, Folder 49)
    - Voir dire sheets- Eric Boynes, Undated (Box 9, Folder 50)
    - Voir dire sheets- Donnell Bennett, Undated (Box 9, Folder 51)
    - Voir dire sheets- Rick bennett, et. Al., 1993 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Voir dire sheets- Antonio betancourt, et. Al., 1991 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Voir dire Sheets- Louis Billa, Undated (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - Voir dire sheets- jesse d. Bond, et. Al., Undated (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Voir dire sheets- james Boone, Undated (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Voir dire sheets- john Bowen, Undated (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Voir dire sheets- Edward Bracey, Undated (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - voir dire sheet- leon bradley, Undated (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - Voir dire sheets- Murray bray, Undated (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - Voir dire sheets- Charles Brown, Undated (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - Voir dire sheets- Christopher Brown, 1997; Undated (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - Voir dire sheets- Gerald Brown, Undated (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - Voir dire sheets- John W. Brown, Undated (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - Voir dire sheets- James R. Bryant, Undated (Box 10, Folder 14)
    - voir Dire sheets- Sean Burke, 1991; Undated (Box 10, Folder 15)
    - voir dire sheets- Esau Burroughs, et. Al., Undated (Box 10, Folder 16)
    - Voir Dire sheets- nathaniel butler, et. Al., Undated (Box 10, Folder 17)
    - Voir dire sheets- John Byrd, et. Al., Undated (Box 10, Folder 18)
    - Voir Dire Sheets- Russell cal, et. Al., Undated (Box 10, Folder 19)
    - Voir Dire Sheets- Ronald comp, Undated (Box 10, Folder 20)
    - Voir Dire sheets- Charles campbell,et. Al., Undated (Box 10, Folder 21)
    - Voir Dire sheets- Gregory campbell, Undated (Box 10, Folder 22)
    - voir Dire Sheets- Danny Carey, 1982 (Box 10, Folder 23)
    - Voir dire sheets- Harold carter, Undated (Box 10, Folder 24)
    - Voir Dire sheets- benjamin Chapman, Undated (Box 10, Folder 25)
    - Voir dire sheets- Robert Chase, Undated (Box 10, Folder 26)
    - voir dire sheet- mark Christian, et. Al., Undated (Box 10, Folder 27)
    - Voir Dire Sheet- leonard Christopher, Undated (Box 10, Folder 28)
    - Voir dire sheets- Ronald clark, Undated (Box 10, Folder 29)
    - Voir dire sheets- Willie Clayton, Undated (Box 10, Folder 30)
    - Voir Dire sheets- patrick Coleman, Undated (Box 10, Folder 31)
    - Voir dire sheets- Rodney Collins, Undated (Box 10, Folder 32)
    - Voir dire sheets- lamont congo, et. Al., Undated (Box 10, Folder 33)
    - Voir dire sheets- Robert cook, 1998 (Box 10, Folder 34)
    - Voir dire sheets- carl M. Cooper, Undated (Box 10, Folder 35)
    - Voir dire sheets- troy Coulston, et. Al., Undated (Box 10, Folder 36)
    - Voir dire sheets- Dewitt crawley, Undated (Box 10, Folder 37)
    - Voir dire sheets- joseph Dallasta, Undated (Box 10, Folder 38)
    - Voir dire sheets- Carmen Damato, Undated (Box 10, Folder 39)
    - Voir dire sheets- Henry Daniels, Undated (Box 10, Folder 40)
    - Voir dire sheets- Allen Dantzler, 1991; Undated (Box 10, Folder 41)
    - Voir dire sheets- mark Davis, et. Al., Undated (Box 10, Folder 42)
    - voir dire sheets- James Dennis, 1997; Undated (Box 10, Folder 43)
    - Voir dire sheets- Joseph Diamatio, et. Al., Undated (Box 10, Folder 44)
    - Voir dire sheets- Raul Diaz, Undated (Box 10, Folder 45)
    - Voir dire sheets- ezzard Dobson, Undated (Box 10, Folder 46)
    - Voir dire sheets- Alfonso Dorsey, et. Al., Undated (Box 10, Folder 47)
    - Voir dire sheets- lamar douglas, et. Al., 1994 (Box 10, Folder 48)
    - Voir Dire sheets- Paul Drayton, Undated (Box 10, Folder 49)
    - Voir Dire Sheets- Donnell Drinks, Undated (Box 10, Folder 50)
    - Voir Dire Sheets- Rafael Droz, et. Al., 1990 (Box 10, Folder 51)
    - Voir Dire Sheets- Mark Eckles, Undated (Box 10, Folder 52)
    - Voir dire sheets- joseph Elliot, Undated (Box 10, Folder 53)
    - Voir Dire Sheets- Robert Felder, Undated (Box 10, Folder 54)
    - Voir Dire sheets- Freddie Feliverty, Undated (Box 10, Folder 55)
    - Voir Dire sheets- Anthony Fletcher, Undated (Box 10, Folder 56)
    - Voir Dire Sheets- Kenneth Ford, Undated (Box 10, Folder 57)
    - Voir Dire Sheets- Thaddeus Ford, et. Al., Undated (Box 10, Folder 58)
    - Voir Dire Sheets- Jesus Garcia, et. Al., Undated (Box 10, Folder 59)
    - voir Dire Sheets- Michael Gaynor, et. Al, Undated (Box 10, Folder 60)
    - Voir Dire Sheets- Ronald Gibson, Undated (Box 10, Folder 61)
    - Voir Dire sheets- Charles Gilyard, 1991; Undated (Box 10, Folder 62)
    - voir Dire Sheets- George Goins, Undated (Box 10, Folder 63)
    - Voir Dire sheets- Devers Gont, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 64)
    - Voir Dire sheets- Robert Grabfelders, et. Al., Undated (Box 10, Folder 65)
    - Voir Dire sheets- Joyce Granger, Undated (Box 10, Folder 66)
    - Voir Dire Sheets- Raymond gray, Undated (Box 10, Folder 67)
    - Voir Dire Sheets- Edward Grazlone, Undated (Box 10, Folder 68)
    - Voir Dire Sheets- James green, Undated (Box 10, Folder 69)
    - Voir Dire Sheets- William Green, Undated (Box 10, Folder 70)
    - voir Dire Sheets- Eric Grier, et. Al., Undated (Box 10, Folder 71)
    - Voir Dire Sheets- Gary Grier, Undated (Box 10, Folder 72)
    - Voir Dire Sheets- Dannielle hadley, Undated (Box 10, Folder 73)
    - voir Dire Sheets- Donald Hall, Undated (Box 10, Folder 74)
    - Voir Dire Sheets- Van Hall, Undated (Box 10, Folder 75)
    - Voir Dire Sheets- Donald Hardcastle, Undated (Box 10, Folder 76)